

□ raedominique.angeles@gmail.com

+(63) 977 812 0096

Noveleta, Cavite

https://rdaangeles.vercel.app/

# **REFERENCES**

# **Edgar Tolete**

Frontend Developer/ Project Manager

Email: edgartolete25@gmail.com

#### Roldan A. Aquino

Kaplan higher education pte ltd, IT Director

Phone: (+65) 92716890

Email: roldan.aquino@kaplan.com

#### **Danmar Varela**

Senior Frontend Developer **Email:** vareladanmarj@gmail.com

# **SKILL**

- HTML./CSS/JavaScript
- SCSS
- Tailwind CSS
- React JS
- Next JS
- Vue JS
- Node JS
- Typescript
- StoryBook
- Liquid
- Figma
- Adobe XD

# Rae Dominique Angeles

Frontend Web Developer

# **PROFILE**

I am a graduate of Computer Science with 5 years of experience working as a Front-End Developer in the industry where I have gained and enhanced my skills in developing user interfaces, testing, debugging, and optimizing web functionalities

I am passionate in programming, always aiming for career advancement and professional development, hard-working in nature, great team player, I have an enthuasiastic demeanour and commitment to the things I am assigned to do. I am always willing and keen to learn more so I can continue to improve my skills, not only technical but also interpersonal.

# **EDUCATION**

Bs Computer Science, New Era University

September 2015 - April 2019

Quezon City, Philippines

Internship - Web Developer (September 2018 - December 2018)

- Helped to achieve a consistent look and visual theme across the website by promoting uniform fonts, formatting, images, and layout.
- Creating Web based scoring system for the University.
- Processing and creating a Client Server Request and Response.
- Resolves minor bug fixes.
- Creates documentation for existing developments on the projects.
- Making requested changes and updates.

# **CERTIFICATION/S**

• HackerRank | Frontend Developer (React) Certificate

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### VTimeTech | Frontend Web Developer

April 2024 - Present

Tech stacks: Next js, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Scss, Storybook

- Became part of a team to develop a CMS for company's innovation.
- Implemented SEO to help websites rank higher in search engines.
- Transforming UI/UX designs into a website application.
- Maintaining the website's functionality based on client requests.
- Create and maintain product documentation.
- Cooperating with backend developers with regards to API integration.
- Cooperate with QA for identifying bugs before executing the application to production.

#### uBind | Product Developer

April 2023 - December 2023

Tech stacks: JavaScript, Adobe XD

- Transforming UX designs into a web form and embed it to client's website.
- Maintaining the form's functionality based on client requests.
- Create and maintain product documentation.
- Create and develop UX Design.
- Cooperate with QA for identifying bugs before executing the application to production.

#### RealPage, Inc. | Frontend Web Developer

January 2021 - March 2023

Tech stacks: JavaScript, Scss, Ruby (erb)

- Transforming web designs into a website.
- Maintaining the website's functionality based on client requests.
- Create and maintain software documentation
- Joined a team to develop an application for company's innovation.
- Cooperate with QA for identifying bugs before executing the application to production.

#### Health Maintenance, Inc. | Full Stack Developer

September 2019 - December 2020

Tech stacks: Vue Js, MySql, Figma

- Transforming web designs into a website.
- Maintaining the website's functionality based on client requests.
- Create and maintain software documentation
- Joined a team to develop an application for company's innovation
- Cooperate with QA for identifying bugs before executing the application to production.

# **PROJECTS**

#### **NOVATED LEASING FORM**

Techonologies: Liquid, Adobe XD

Created a UX design of a form for a leasing company and translate it to an interactable web form where it allows user to get an estimated premium of the insurance based on the user's answer in the form.

#### **BOKKEEPERS FORM**

Techonologies: Adobe XD

Created a UX design of a form for a bookkeeping insurance company where it allows user to get an estimated premium of the insurance based on the user's answer in the form.

#### **NETFLIX-CLONE**

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css, Firebase

A netflix clone web application where users can create an account, log in using their created account and saved movies/shows. Created account and saved movie/show is stored in Firebase

Site: https://netflix-clone-chi-neon.vercel.app/

#### **PEDAL DECK**

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css, Redux

A frontend design of an e-commerce website that allows user to browse a bicycle and check its information. It also allows them to add on their cart and proceed to checking out.

Site: https://pedal-deck.web.app

#### SIROTER-LE-DELICIEUX-CAFE

Technologies: React JS, Tailwind Css, Redux

A frontend design of a coffee shop website that allows users to determine its information as well as look into its different services and products that the shop offers.

Site: <a href="https://siroter-le-delicieux-cafe.vercel.app/">https://siroter-le-delicieux-cafe.vercel.app/</a>

#### **HEALTH MAINTENANCE INC | PORTAL AND WEBSITE**

Techonologies: Vue JS, Scss, Node Js and MySQL

**Portal:** A Progressive Web App that allows users to view utilities/transaction history from their previous activity. Users can also view their profile as well as their dependencies.

**Website:** A company website that helps users know what the company is all about, who are the management team and its services. Also, the website allows users to search their affiliated facilities and physicians.

Site (Portal): <a href="https://portal.hmi.com.ph/">https://portal.hmi.com.ph/</a>
Site (Website): <a href="https://www.hmi.com.ph/">https://www.hmi.com.ph/</a>